Contact

0341-2636750 (Mobile) m.anas.amin@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/anasamin-7a18bb24 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Spring MVC Ruby on Rails ASP.NET MVC

Languages

English (Professional Working)
Urdu (Native or Bilingual)

Anas Amin

Consultant at FAIR Consulting Group

Pakistan

Summary

Working as a Software Engineer for the past 5 years mostly on web applications and covering the entire stack. My experience spans multiple web development platforms and that has honed my self-learning skills. I have recently ventured into serverless architecture and love the flexibility and simplicity.

Experience

FAIR Consulting Group Consultant July 2021 - Present (4 months) Karāchi, Sindh, Pakistan

FAIR Consulting Group is a Management and IT consulting firm that focuses on Customer Experience (CX). We live and breathe one core value, to always be 'FAIR - to our Employees, Customers, Partners and the Community'.

We offer end to end engagement to our customers, with an uncompromising focus on quality to ensure that we deliver the best possible CX outcomes.

By focusing on solutions that realise immediate business value as a priority, we are able to turn CX strategies into defined processes supported by best practice methodologies and relevant systems.

Learn more about how we empower our customers in their digital transformation journey at our website, www.faircg.com

KASB Securities
Development Team Lead
April 2021 - June 2021 (3 months)
Karāchi, Sindh, Pakistan

Responsible for Designing and Conceptualizing backend services

Auriga Solutions
Senior Software Engineer
March 2016 - March 2021 (5 years 1 month)

Page 1 of 2

Karachi

Conceptualizing and developing web-based software solutions and working on the full stack on a variety of platforms that includes AWS, ASP.NET, Vue.js, Elastic Search, SQL Server, and Angular 4.

GoodCore Software, Inc Software Engineer July 2014 - March 2016 (1 year 9 months) Karachi

Engineered web applications and worked on multiple MVC platforms including RoR, php Yii, and Spring MVC.

Education

National University of Computer and Emerging Sciences Master's degree, Data Science · (2017 - 2020)

FAST-NUCES
BS-CS, Computer Science · (2010 - 2014)

St. Bonaventure's High School Matriculation · (1997 - 2008)